Donald and Charlotte MacJannet Papers MS024
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs and other media, 1880 -- 2000; 1915 -- 1999; MS024.007; 34.95 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 58 Audiovisual Object(s); 727 Digital Object(s)
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet on vacation, 1935; MS024.007.DO.04452; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    People; Bridges (built works); Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf
  - Aunt Lotte (Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet) at Upper Camp, 1935; MS024.007.DO.04453; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet Camp (upper camp)
  - Father (Otto Blensdorf), Eva (Muller-Blensdorf) and Aunt Lotte (Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet) at upper camp, 1935; MS024.007.DO.04454; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; Blensdorf, Otto; Muller-Blensdorf, Eva
  - Charlotte Blensdorf and sister, 1907; MS024.007.DO.04455; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Children; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf
  - Uncle Donald (MacJannet) with mustache, 1935; MS024.007.DO.04456; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
  - Charlotte and Donald MacJannet on a mountainside, 1936; MS024.007.DO.04457; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    People; Mountains; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Donald Ross
  - Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, 1940; MS024.007.DO.04458; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet at the beach, 1932; MS024.007.DO.04459; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
  - Dalcroze method dancers, 1925; MS024.007.DO.04460; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    People; Dances and Dancing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet in Jenna, 1935; MS024.007.DO.04461; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
  - Charlotte Blensdorf (MacJannet), 1925; MS024.007.DO.04462; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
  - Mary van Bibber Harris, European Center Director 1984-89, 1982; MS024.007.DO.04628; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Removed from MS024/007-96
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; photographic print; Harris, Mary van Bibber; European Center
  - Professor Seymour Simches at the dedication ceremony of the Prieuré as European Center, 1979; MS024.007.DO.04629; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Simches, Seymour O.; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; European Center
  - Donald MacJannet, Rocky Carzo and students at the Prieuré, Talloires, 1982; MS024.007.DO.04630; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Removed from MS024/007-97. From Bertrand Xavier Soret.
    Students; People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Donald Ross; Carzo, Rocco "Rocky"; European Center
  - Rob Hollister, Donald MacJannet. Charlotte MacJannet in Geneva, 1983; MS024.007.DO.04631; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Removed from MS024/007-97
    People; Faculty; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Hollister, Rob; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Donald Ross
  - Mary van Bibber Harris, Donald MacJannet, and Charlotte MacJannet, 1985; MS024.007.DO.04632; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Removed from MS024/007-95.
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Harris, Mary van Bibber; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Donald Ross
  - Mary van Bibber Harris cuts the ribbon for the MacGames alongside Donald and Charlotte MacJannet and Rocky Carzo, 1984; MS024.007.DO.04633; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Removed from MS024/007-96.
    People; Athletics; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Harris, Mary van Bibber; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Donald Ross; Carzo, Rocco "Rocky"; European Center
  - Donald MacJannet, 1975; MS024.007.DO.04634; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
  - Mary van Bibber Harris cuts the ribbon for the MacGames alongside Donald MacJannet, Charlotte MacJannet and Rocky Carzo, 1984; MS024.007.DO.04635; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Removed from MS024/007-97#7
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; Athletics; photographic print; Harris, Mary van Bibber; MacJannet, Donald Ross; Carzo, Rocco "Rocky"; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; European Center
  - Charlotte MacJannet surrounded by Tufts students, 1988; MS024.007.DO.04636; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    People; Students; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; European Center; Tufts University
  - Mr. Mac and Betty Mayer, ca. 1980, MS024.007.DO.04637; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Donald Ross; Mayer, Elizabeth Van Huysen
  - Donald MacJannet, amateur photographer in action, 1975; MS024.007.DO.04638; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; photographic print; MacJannet, Donald Ross
  - MacJannet campers at the Tour de France, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05038; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Gift of Bill Rough.
    Children; Cycling; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - Donald MacJannet points the way for a hike on Mt. Blanc glacier, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05039; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; Children; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet camper Denis Manuel, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05040; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Children; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - Annecy, France, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05041; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph)
  - Donald MacJannet after the plum tree storm, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05042; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; Trees; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet counselor Bill Rough on Lake Annecy, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05043; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; Swimming; Lakes; slide (photograph); Rough, William; MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet camper Charles Russell in the chalet, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05044; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Children; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet campers ready to tackle the mountain, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05045; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Gift of Bill Rough. MacJannet camper Greg Nelson on left.
    Children; Mountains; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet camper Charles Russell on Lake Annecy, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05046; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Children; Canoes and canoeing; Lakes; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet campers Tiger Bailey and Charles Russell, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05047; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
  - MacJannet campers on a hike, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05048; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Children; Mountains; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet campers ready for chalet inspection, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05049; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Gift of Bill Rough. Left row: ?, Charles Russell, Tiger Bailey. Right row: Denis Manuel, Henri Magnard, ?.
    Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet campers watch the Tour de France go by, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05050; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Cycling; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - Town of Annecy, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05051; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
  - A MacJannet camper puts away his clothes, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05052; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
  - Lake Annecy, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05053; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Lakes; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - Sunset at the MacJannet Camp, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05054; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Lakes; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet camper hike through the woods, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05075; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Children; Forests; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - View from a MacJannet Camp climb from the mountains towards Lake Annecy, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05076; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Mountains; Lakes; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet campers admire the view, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05077; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
  - MacJannet campers on the shores of Lake Annecy, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05078; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
  - The dive, MacJannet Camp, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05079; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Lakes; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - A MacJannet camper strolls along Lake Annecy, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05080; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Children; Swans; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet camper Charles Russell enjoys the view, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05081; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Mountains; Views; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet campers organize for a day out, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05082; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Children; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet campers in their chalet, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05083; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Gift of Bill Rough. Left to right: ?, Charles Russell, Denis Manuel, Henri Magnard.
  - MacJannet Camp boys chalets, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05084; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
  - View of Les Dents de Lanfon, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05085; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Mountains; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet counselors at Mont Blanc, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05086; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Mountains; Views; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - View down to Lake Annecy and Chateau de St. Bernard, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05087; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Mountains; Views; Lakes; Castles; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet upper camp, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05088; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Mountains; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet Camp at Mont Blanc, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05089; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
  - MacJannet counselor Bill Rough overlooks Lake Annecy, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05090; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Mountains; Lakes; Views; People; slide (photograph); Rough, William; MacJannet Camp
  - Camp fire at MacJannet upper camp, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05091; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
  - Amos Booth, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05092; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; slide (photograph); Booth, Amos; MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet campers swimming in Lake Annecy, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05093; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Swimming; Lakes; Children; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - View across the lake of the MacJannet Camp, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05094; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
  - MacJannet Camp meeting in the chalet, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05095; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet Campers, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05096; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Gift of Bill Rough. Back row: ?, Tiger Bailey, ?. Front: Denis Manuel, Henri Magnard.
  - MacJannet campers hiking, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05097; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    Gift of Bill Rough. Camper Tiger Bailey in the lead.
    Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Mountains; People; Children; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet Camp counselors, 1959; MS024.007.DO.05108; Rough, William (Box Shared 41)
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
- MacJannet Legacy Oral History Interviews and donated items of memory, 1916 -- 2003; 2003; MS024.008; 0.95 Linear Feet; 2 Audiovisual Object(s)
  The DCA MacJannet Legacy project created a website using the material and information within the Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers collection. As part of the project, oral history interviews with former MacJannet students, campers, scholarship recipients and others were conducted from December 2002 through August 2003 by project coordinator Maura Kenny. These interviews, while not part of the Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers are a valuable source of information concerning the matters of the collection
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Gus Naismith and George Halsey, 2002-12-10 -- 2003-01-07; MS024.008.243.00001 (Box 243)
    Side a: Gus Naismith, part 1/1, interviewed at the Tufts Digital Collection and Archives. Side b: George Halsey, part 3/3, interviewed at his home in Boston, MA. Digital versions of interview: gusnaismith.wav and georgehalsey.wav.
  - George Halsey, 2003-01-07; MS024.008.243.00002 (Box 243)
    Side a: 1/3 and side b: 2/3 interview of George Halsey, January 7, 2003 at his home in Boston, MA. Digital version georgehalsey.wav.
  - Mary van Bibber Harris, 2003-01-14; MS024.008.243.00003 (Box 243)
    Side a: 1/2 and side b: 2/2, Mary Harris interviewed at the Tufts Digital Collection and Archives. Digital version maryvanbibberharris.wav
  - Bill Rough, 2003-02-27; MS024.008.243.00004 (Box 243)
    Side a: 1/2 and side b: 2/2 of Bill Rough interviewed at the Princeton Club, New York City. Digital version billrougha.wav and billroughb.wav.
  - Alan Reeves, 2003-03-04; MS024.008.244.00001 (Box 244)
    Side a: part 1/5 and side b: part 2/5 of interview with Alan Reeves at the King George Hotel, San Francisco, CA. Digital version alanreeves.wav.
  - Alan Reeves, 2003-03-04; MS024.008.244.00002 (Box 244)
    Side a: part 3/5 and side b: part 4/5 of interview with Alan Reeves at the King George Hotel, San Francisco, CA. Digital version alanreeves.wav.
  - Alan Reeves, 2003-03-04; MS024.008.244.00003 (Box 244)
    Side a: part 5/5 of interview with Alan Reeves at the King George Hotel, San Francisco, CA. Digital version alanreeves.wav.
  - Sally Pym, 2003-03-04; MS024.008.244.00004 (Box 244)
    Side a: part 1/1 of interview with Sally Pym at the King George Hotel, San Francisco, CA. Digital version sallypym.wav.
  - Tony Farrell and Gary Friedman, 2003-03-05; MS024.008.245.00001 (Box data_value_missing_e9cd1be6ae1288363a7130fe97883a48)
    Side a: part 1/1 of interview of Tony Farrell at his office in San Francisco, CA. Side b: part 1/1 of interview with Gary Friedman at his office in Mill Valley, CA. Digital versions tonyfarrell.wav and friedman.wav.
  - Janice Farrell Day and Christopher Farrell, 2003-03-07; MS024.008.245.00002 (Box data_value_missing_e9cd1be6ae1288363a7130fe97883a48)
    Side a: part 1/1 of interview with Janice Day and Christopher Farrell in St. Paul, MN. Digital version janiceandchristopherfarrell.wav
  - Mildred Pond, 2003-03-10; MS024.008.245.00003 (Box data_value_missing_e9cd1be6ae1288363a7130fe97883a48)
    Side a: part 1/1 of interview with Mildred Pond in her home in New Preston, CT. Digital version mildredpond.wav
  - Alan Duke, 2003-06-04; MS024.008.245.00004 (Box data_value_missing_e9cd1be6ae1288363a7130fe97883a48)
    Side a: Part 1/1 of interview with Alan Duke at the Bishop's Office, Canterbury Cathedral, UK. Digital version alanduke.wav.
  - Oral history interview agreements, 2002; MS024.008.246.00001 (Box 246)
  - Images from Prieure poster exhibit, 1985; MS024.008.246.00002 (Box 246)
  - Tony Farrell's camp letter, 1963; MS024.008.246.00003 (Box 246)
  - MacJannet camper's Bill Romey's book, Plus ca change, 1996; MS024.008.246.00004 (Box 246)
  - "Souvernirs" by Suzanne Lans, 1994; MS024.008.246.00005 (Box 246)
  - Doris Berger's photos of Mrs. Mac, 1995; MS024.008.246.00006 (Box 246)
  - Memoirs of Howard Cook, 1990; MS024.008.246.00007 (Box 246)
  - Copy of Donald and Charlotte MacJannet's marriage certificate, 2003; MS024.008.246.00008 (Box 246)
    Obtained from the Westminster Registry Office, June 2003.
  - MacJannet Legacy project guest book, 2002; MS024.008.246.00009 (Box 246)
  - MacJannet Camp photos from Bill Rough, 1961; MS024.008.247.00001 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - MacJannet Camp photos from Bill Rough, 1961; MS024.008.247.00002 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - MacJannet Camp photos from Bill Rough, 1961; MS024.008.247.00003 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - MacJannet Camp photos from Bill Rough, 1961; MS024.008.247.00004 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - MacJannet Camp photos from Bill Rough, 1961; MS024.008.247.00005 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - MacJannet Camp photos from Bill Rough, 1961; MS024.008.247.00006 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - MacJannet Camp photos from Bill Rough, 1961; MS024.008.247.00007 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - MacJannet Camp photos from Bill Rough, 1961; MS024.008.247.00008 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - MacJannet Camp photos from Bill Rough, 1961; MS024.008.247.00009 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - MacJannet Camp photos from Bill Rough, 1961; MS024.008.247.00010 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Photos from Sally Pym of the MacJannet house in Arlington, 1944 -- 1952; MS024.008.247.00011 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Photos from Charlotte MacJannet's niece Gonda Harvey, 1930 -- 1950; MS024.008.247.00012 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Photos from Sally Pym, 1979; MS024.008.247.00013 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Priory groups, 1980; MS024.008.247.00014 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Mr. MacJannet, from Sally pym, 1982; MS024.008.247.00015 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Photos from Priscilla Barclay, 1965; MS024.008.247.00016 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Photos from Amos Booth, 1960; MS024.008.247.00017 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Slides from Bill Rough, 1959; MS024.008.247.00018 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Slides from Bill Rough, 1959; MS024.008.247.00019 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Slides from Bill Rough, 1959; MS024.008.247.00020 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Donald MacJannet as a young pilot, 1918; MS024.008.248.00001 (Box 248)
    photographic print
  - Personal photos, 1916 -- 1940; MS024.008.248.00002 (Box 248)
  - Susanne Lanse and Charlotte MacJannet, 1970; MS024.008.248.00003 (Box 248)
  - MacJannet School (St. Cloud/The Ems) photos, 1930; MS024.008.248.00004 (Box 248)
  - MacJannet Camp photos, 1930; MS024.008.248.00005 (Box 248)
  - Interview with MacJannet, 1980; MS024.008.249.00001 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Interview with Grace Lee Billings, 1990; MS024.008.249.00002 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Interview with D. MacJannet, 1990; MS024.008.249.00003 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Narration of MacJannet Film, 1990; MS024.008.249.00004 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
    Commentary on MacJannet Film either by Charlotte MacJannet or by the film's creator.
  - Interview with Wenke Thoman Sterns and Tony Kleitz, 1990; MS024.008.249.00005 (Box data_value_missing_ae1e766ca5247cd85f69aa1b5ccff832)
  - Interview with Mervyn & Carole Puleston, 2003; MS024.008.249.00006 (Box 249)
    Kidlington, OK
  - Interview with Rob Hollister, 2003; MS024.008.249.00007 (Box 249)
    Medford, Massachusetts, Tufts University
  - Interview with Tony Cook, 2003; MS024.008.249.00008 (Box 249)
    Talloires, France
  - Interview with Rocco Carzo, 2003; MS024.008.249.00009 (Box 249)
  - Interview with Stowe Phelps and Fernand Bise, 2003; MS024.008.249.00010 (Box 249)
    Stowe Phelps was interviewed at his apartment in New York City on Aprill 11, 2003. Fernand Bise was interviewed at his hotel in Talloires, France on June 10, 2003.
  - Interview with Cynthia Raymond and Dan Rottenberg, 2003; MS024.008.249.00011 (Box 249)
    Cynthia Raymond was interviewed in Tallories, France on June 22, 2003. Dan Rottenberg was interviewed in Talloires, France in June 2003.
  - Interview with Doug Marston, 2003; MS024.008.249.00012 (Box 249)
    Talloires/Prieure France
  - Interview with John Iglehart, 2003; MS024.008.249.00013 (Box 249)
    Geneva, Switzerland
  - Interview with Francois Grand Mangin, 2003; MS024.008.249.00014 (Box 249)
    Talloires/Prieure France, in French
  - Interview with Gabruella Goldstein, 2003; MS024.008.249.00015 (Box 249)
  - Interview with Robert Jerome, 2003; MS024.008.249.00016 (Box 249)
  - Interview with Jean-Marie Herve, 2003; MS024.008.249.00017 (Box 249)
- Additional accessions, 1938 -- 2000; MS024.009; 1 Volumes
  Physical condition. Open for research.
  - MacJannet films, MS024-001 (Box 1)
  - MacJannet films, MS024-002 (Box 2)
  - Two Camp films, 1938 -- 1939; MS024-024 (Box 3)
    Physical condition.
    MacJannett camp files donated by Rocky Carzo. In need of preservation work and migration.
  - Papers belonging to Howard Cook, 1968 -- 2000; MS024-233 (Box 4)
  - Papers belonging to Howard Cook, 1968 -- 2000; MS024-234 (Box 5)
  - MacJannet Foundation papers from Rocky Carzo, 1990 -- 2000; MS024-235 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence and video via Gabriella Goldstein, 1979 -- 2000; MS024-236 (Box 7)
    Correspondence between MacJannet's and Seymour Simches.